[{"answer": "It's not easy.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "What is your take on what is happening?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "You know, just 11 years ago I was prime minister of Israel and together with President Clinton we put a far reaching kind of a proposal on the -- on the table.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Doesn't there eventually have to be a cutoff point here?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't understand exactly what he meant, in what context he's --", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Do you agree with what Rick Perry said?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "You know, I think, first of all, he's president of America.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Is he a friend of Israel?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I think that I do not pretend to enter into the American political debate.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Is it inflammatory?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "That's up to -- that's up to the American people.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "If he comes out with these kind of statement, isn't that dangerous?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I believe Prime Minister Netanyahu genuinely believes in the need to move forward and ready to take the risks to pay the painful price.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "I mean the moment the Palestinians are circumnavigating you to the United Nations, is it not the time, as many people are crying out for, for you and Prime Minister Netanyahu to get together and say, we're going to make this happen, we're going to do a deal, we're going to take more pain in negotiation than we would wish to because the bigger picture is more important?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "It's -- you know, Israel, we -- for example, we pulled out under my order as a prime minister from Lebanon.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What is the risk that you're talking about?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "It's clear we have to rely upon ourselves, that it's a tough neighborhood.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What is it like to be the Israeli defense minister in the middle of all this?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Let me tell you -- I feel the pain for Mubarak.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "-- with a whole lot of Irans?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "First of all, we are worried, but a person cannot choose his parents, and a nation cannot choose its neighbors.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Like I said, do you worry that you may end up with a series of mini-Irans coming out of this Arab Spring where you have the Islamists basically controlling these countries in a way they never have before?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "It was the time 10 years and 20 years.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "This is the time to do this deal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "See, only time will tell.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you feel after all these decades you dealt with Palestinian leadership, that the current leadership, even if they don't have complete control over all the elements with the Palestinians, do you feel there is more chance now of doing a deal with the people at the head, Palestinian leadership, than you've had in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Still have to be proven.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Does your gut instinct tell you that?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, it is the biggest moment of my career.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, if you remember, when you and I first started working together on \"Britain's Got Talent,\" God only knows how that happened.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Yes, I mean, someone supremely self-confident like you, how nervous are you?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, it's like comparing you and I. We're both guys, we're both British, but there's a massive difference between how people respond to you and people respond to me.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "And from what you've edited so far, how confident are you that it's going to be a big hit?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, at times.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Is there any truth to the ghastly rumor that you're quite nice in this series or not?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "It's crazily good.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "From what you've seen now -- you've gone through the auditions -- how good is the talent on U.S. \"X Factor\"?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, you don't go into anything contemplating failure, because if you did, you wouldn't make it.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "And how would you deal with it?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "It's impossible to predict.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Could you take down \"Idol,\" do you think, in season one?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Did you watch many of the \"Idol\" shows?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Did you find it odd, the whole concept of an \"Idol\" without you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "He's there.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Mr. Mean is still there, isn't he, alive and kicking?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I had to sort myself out.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "To those who've lost their jobs in all this, who are really suffering out there, what do you say to them?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "But you shouldn't an opinion.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What are you talking about?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Because we don't live here.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "As a leader, I think he's a decent guy, I really do.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "As a leader, how do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I can't do it, but I watch it.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "You're not on Twitter, are you?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "You're fanatical about big lights and listened to.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "You're not worried about not getting as many followers as me?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I don't mind you exchanging barbs.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "How impossible has she been to work with?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "In a nice way.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "How am I impossible?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Have you ever met a bigger ego than Simon?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "You know, I started out in a show like this, where I entered the audition, went through the whole process, and went to the city and drove there.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "It must for the nerves alone make things ten times more tense?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "I don't like watching myself on TV.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Why are you so awkward watching it?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "It's much easier to perform.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I have heard it all.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Not everybody is like you, Simon, OK?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Growing up, I loved Paula, like I was kind of obsessed with Paula.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Can we talk about Paula Abdul, because obviously, you know, an old -- what does it feel like you, Nicole, to be coming in between the most famous talent show judging desk pairing in history?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Well, let me show you.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "That's the thing, is like my -- my papa is a priest.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Do your family slightly go, Nicole, what are you up to?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "My grandfather.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Your dad loved that video?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "They love it.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I have a boyfriend.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "And the crushing answer is no, you're not, are you?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "-- I have ever experienced.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "When you first met his, was it love at first hand bite?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "I don't -- that would be weird, right?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Yes, he's a great guy, very cool, brilliant driver, but a cool guy.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "You know Louis, right?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "He is very humble.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Is that what you need in your life?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Does he quite qualify for toy boy status or not?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "This is not that kind of show, not the kind of show that you do.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "I'm really excited.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Are you excited by this?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "A little bit, yeah.", "docId": "110920pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "You got a little crush, don't you ?", "qSentId": 675}]